[Episode 7]
Minju...
Didn't I warn you before?
That if you don't have the guts,
you shouldn't get involved with me.
Minju...
It's been a while. What are you doing here?
Did you eat?
I didn't see anything, okay?
I didn't have breakfast yet,
so you came at just the right time.
Let's go.
Come with me.
Where?
To Yun's.
Why should I?
I'll leave.
If it's because of the scandal and it's hard for you,
I'll disappear from Yun's sight.
Eunchae...
So stop playing around and let's go.
I don't want anyone to recognize you.
You can breathe, right?
Taxi! Taxi!
- Taxi!
- I don't want to!
Stay still.
Eunchae.
Yun!
Yun, Minju is here.
How have you been?
I'm not mad at you.
Considering how much you put up
with what a player I've been,
how can I be mad at you?
I don't have the right.
I was afraid it was Eunchae you needed.
That's why I was upset.
I'm not jealous. Just being honest.
Why would you say that?
How could you say something like that about
me and Eunchae?
That makes absolutely no sense. Don't you know that?
Eunchae likes you, Yun.
Eunchae loves you.
What?
Hey, Blockhead!
Come hang out with me.
Sure. Let's hang out.
I didn't do anything wrong! I really don't know!
How would I know the bus number going to Maljuk Street?
Why are you so rude?
Stop it, you old geezer. Stop it!
I'm going to break your cane.
What? Oh, yeah? Fine! Just break it! Break it!
Mister, give me that cane.
Give me that cane!
Hey!
I'm sorry, please forgive him. I'm so sorry.
Okay, okay. Sure, sure.
I could just kill you, you little...
I'm so sorry.
I can't get hit on the head.
Damn old geezer!
I knew this day would come.
You don't know proper Korean, and have no respect.
You're lucky that this is
the only punishment you got.
If it were me, I would have shown you no mercy.
None at all!
How can I possibly train you, you animal?
Say "thank you."
Fine. I'm leaving.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Say please and thank you often.
Please. Thank you.
May I have please have a glass of water?
How can I help you?
If you're not sure, ask. And always say, "Please."
Please?
Let's try. Ask me for a cup of water.
May I have a cup of water... Please?
How would you ask for help?
Would you please help me?
What next...
What if I gave you my seat?
Awesome!
No! You say, "Thank you!"
How is she your wife if you're not married?
Where is your wife now?
She married Jason.
What do you mean?
I'm done being polite.
The end!
So... Your wife
betrayed you and married someone else?
You poor thing...
I'll carry it for you.
- I got it.
- Thank you!
So smart! I teach you one thing,
and you pick up on all the rest.
Hey, Yun.
You like me?
What?
You're attracted to me? Have you gone crazy?
What are you talking about?
Get here right this minute!
Yun, I'm far from home.
Then come in 30 seconds.
It's just over there.
It's just right there.
Come on.
We're nearly there.
Here, I'll give you a few apples.
Blockhead!
Song Eunchae.
Yun.
I love you, Eunchae,
with all of my body, with all my soul, Song Eunchae.
Yun...
What are you doing?
Wow... Your heart's really racing, you brat!
How could you? How could this be?
What on earth are you talking about?
You like me? You love me?
Who said that?
Minju.
I'm going to kill that brat.
You can't do that.
This is ridiculous.
We're family! We're like siblings!
We're like family.
Wake up, Eunchae!
Even if you stood naked in front of me,
I wouldn't bat an eye.
Neither of us can ever be attracted to the other!
Just wait! I'll introduce you to a great guy!
[Yun]
It's me.
Can you fill the car trunk full of balloons
by early morning tomorrow?
I have a man.
I mean a fiance.
What?
Actually I wanted to introduce him to you.
Let's all go out. The four of us.
Are you kidding me?
It's true.
Then what does he do?
He's a businessman.
He lives in a really nice apartment in Gangnam.
He's rich, kind, handsome, and really sophisticated.
He's my ideal man.
I should have told you earlier.
I'm sorry for the mixup.
[Eunchae]
Your call is being forwarded to voicemail...
Who are you calling?
That guy who has a crush on me.
Yun's manager?
Yeah. I left him yesterday without telling him.
He must have searched all over for me.
I saw him yesterday. He seems really sleazy.
He's been through a lot.
So... What are you going to do?
If I asked him to go out with me again,
he'd think I was crazy, right?
He'd think I was just toying with him, don't you think?
Eunchae!
I was tossing and turning all last
night thinking about it and I don't
think I'll ever find someone who'll
like me as much as he likes me.
It's because of Yun, isn't it?
So now you've decided to latch onto any old guy?
Do you really want to ruin your life that way?
I give up!
Maybe you should fight Minju for Yun.
You're no match for her.
Is it that obvious?
When you look at me,
is it that obvious that I like him?
Because you're born as a girl,
there's no way for you to fight it.
How can you not love Yun? He's so hot.
But you can't be with just anyone.
Not that guy, especially.
I already kissed him. We already slept together too.
Are you living in the Joseon Dynasty?
When I look at him,
I feel like I'm looking at myself.
He is shy, awkward, and
can't quite express his feelings right.
I feel sorry for him.
You're nuts!
Who is she talking about?
Yun's manager. That lame, sleazy guy.
You can't! He's mine! I got dibs!
Where's the furthest place from Korea?
Where there's no chance for me to
hear any news about Korea.
In this age of globalism? No. Maybe. Africa?
I said he's mine! I got dibs!
Africa?
[Missed call]
Is everything ready? The favor I asked of you?
Yeah.
Then come to Minju's place! Now!
Okay.
It's done, right?
So when Minju comes from there to here,
we just have to open the trunk.
I hope she doesn't get confused. I'm nervous.
How do I look?
Minju has to be moved!
She will be touched!
If Minju accepts my proposal,
I will treat you to something!
Okay.
Thank you! You're free to go now.
Oh, Yun. You're here? Just come up then.
Really? Okay, I'll be down in ten minutes.
What do you think you're doing? Let go!
What is this place?
Can't you read?
Do I seem that easy to you?
Even though I'm a bit of a player,
I have really high standards!
I warned you that if you don't have the guts,
not to get involved with me.
I won't ever look for you again.
Let's have dinner together.
Come with me. I have a room at Seoul Hotel.
Sorry, Yun. I have something urgent to do.
I'm not home. I'll call you later.
[Minju! Marry me.]
Your call is being forwarded to voicemail.
Blockhead!
Who are you?
Who are you... ma'am?
I'm Eunchae's older sister.
Why are you answering Eunchae's phone, ma'am?
She threw her phone away.
Where did she go?
She said she wanted to travel before moving to Africa.
Africa?
Yes, Africa.
Blockhead!
Mister!
I asked for your address from your employer.
I came to say goodbye.
I'm going somewhere far away.
I'm not sure when I'll be coming back,
So I wanted to say goodbye.
Oh, by the way...
Here. I should have returned it earlier.
Thank you.
I'll never forget you. Please forget me.
Find yourself a good woman.
Make me kimchi before you go!
My sister makes really good seaweed rolls,
but she doesn't make good kimchi.
Make me kimchi before you go.
I can't make kimchi.
I'm sorry.
Well, I can make radish kimchi.
You were adopted by Australian parents?
- You just found your sister?
- Yeah.
What about your parents? Did you find them, too?
How could she? She abandoned both her children?
Stuff happens.
Maybe she was too poor to even feed me milk
and gave me up so I could have a better life.
That was probably it.
Wait.
Well, you are nice. You learned Korean.
You like kimchi.
I'm so proud of you, mister.
Isn't that a bit too much?
This is how you're supposed to make it.
This is a beautiful color.
So this is radish kimchi?
How did it become like this?
Eat one more!
Where's Eunchae?
Where is Eunchae?
Move! I have to make the bed.
Where's Eunchae?
How should I know? She left her phone.
What kind of mother are you?
How do you not know where she is?
Audrey! Audrey!
Malbok! Jo Malbok!
What did you say?
Didn't I say never to call me by that name ever again?
You're called "Audrey" outside,
but here, you're still Malbok.
I am Audrey, here or there.
I am Audrey everywhere.
I'm Audrey.
Please!
Oh, gosh!
Your son wants some breast milk. Give him some!
What's wrong, my son?
- Eunchae is missing.
- What?
She told my boss that she was going to quit.
What? What's going on with her?
I don't know!
She said she's going to Africa.
Africa?
What? Then what about me?
What about me?
What do you mean? What about you?
I didn't want to say this,
but I heard from Minchae that
she didn't want to make you uncomfortable.
She left for you and Minju.
So you guys can be happy.
What?
My poor daughter.
I'm sorry for being such a bad mother.
If we had enough money,
we'd move out of this house!
I can't clean like this... You do it!
What?
What is she talking about?
Eunchae must really have been in love with me.
What?
Crazy girl.
I should leave before he gets out of the bathroom.
Goodbye, Mister.
Stop crying, Mom.
Stop crying, Mom. It's okay.
If there was a crazy dog after me,
I would pee my pants, too.
It's okay.
Who are you?
I'm the friend of the guy who lives here.
Uncle!
Why is your mom crying again?
Because she peed in her pants.
Because a crazy dog was after her
and she was scared.
Galchi!
I'm sorry. I wasn't supposed to say
that she peed on herself.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
Good job. Great job.
You're so cool.
Why are you crying? Stop crying!
Yun Seo-kyeong!
You're terrible!
Why are you screaming at your sister?
Why don't you shut up?
You just don't get it, do you?
You're terrible!
Seo-kyeong.
I pee my pants all the time.
I peed my pants a couple nights ago.
And not just on my pants but on the blanket, too.
Do you pee on the blanket?
I don't pee on the blanket.
Then you're better than me.
You don't hear about it much
but a lot of adults pee their pants.
It's even in the newspaper. You didn't know that?
Here, I'll help you. Do you want to wash up?
Wait. Let's wash up together. Let's go.
Your hair's so pretty. You should perm it.
Have you gotten a perm before?
Oh yeah, we didn't put on lotion.
I thought my face felt a bit dry.
Please give me some lotion.
I don't have lotion.
You don't have lotion?
You've never put on lotion before?
Nope.
Don't go.
Don't go, Eunchae.
I won't burden you. Please don't go.
Eunchae really likes you, Yun.
She's in love with you.
Just kill me, why don't you?
Song Eunchae... Just kill me already!
Yes, I'm the new coordinator.
I don't know. They said Song Eunchae quit.
Yeah. I'll get you an autograph.
I have to go.
Hi, I am Jang Suhi.
She's the new coordinator.
Seaweed rolls! Seaweed rolls for sale!
Rice cakes! Rice cakes for sale!
Warm, fresh seaweed rolls!
Welcome!
Seaweed rolls for sale! Warm seaweed rolls!
Warm seaweed rolls for sale!
Sir, buy some seaweed rolls!
Seaweed rolls for sale!
- Seaweed rolls for sale!
- And rice cakes!
Do you like it?
Yeah.
You look really good with short hair. Just a second.
Choi Yun.
- Minju.
- Surprised?
You're my partner today?
Today's concept is the New Year's Special.
I have to be here.
I wanted to surprise you,
so I asked them to keep it a secret.
Wow! You're so beautiful, wifey!
Your mom didn't come?
She's at the salon. She'll be here soon.
And Eunchae?
I don't know. That traitor.
Don't ever mention that brat's name
in front of me ever again.
Wow! How pretty!
- Galchi, isn't your mom pretty?
- Yes!
Wow, you're so pretty!
Is it yummy?
You want to wear a nice dress
and get married, too, huh?
Is there someone you like?
Yes.
Who?
Tell me.
Uncle.
Huh?
You drive me crazy! How would you marry Uncle?
He's just an uncle!
You can't marry him. Right, Eunchae?
- You mean Muhyeok?
- Yes.
No. I can marry him. I will.
No, you can't. Uncle is... Oh, geez!
Why is my mom such a dummy? So frigging...
"Frigging"? I'm going to marry him!
Minju, you did a great job today!
How was I today?
- Great!
- So pretty!
Are you done yet?
Why? Where are you? It's so loud.
We're at karaoke with Mom, Eunchae and Grandpa.
Sing!
Sing a song! Sing a song!
Go, go!
Sing! Sing!
Sing a song!
This is ridiculous.
We're family! We're like siblings!
Uncle, sing a song!
Galchi. The national anthem.
Mister, are you okay?
Eunchae.
Can I ask you a favor?
What?
Don't go to Africa.
Could you take care of my sister and Galchi
later when I am not here?
Are you going somewhere? Back to Australia?
Why don't you stay here with your family?
You said that you didn't have anyone back there.
Your wife is already married.
It's cold. Let's go in.
I wanted to hug you once.
Last time I didn't. So I'll hug you now.
Is that okay?
Are you warm?
You're not lonely anymore right?
[Episode 8 Preview]
Did you hide it in your clothes? Huh?
Where is my sister? Did she go home?
[Sorry, I can no longer be forgiven]
You messed up today.
To Seo-kyeong and Muhyeok.
You did them wrong, big time.
- Are you insane?
- No, I'm not insane.
She wouldn't know she gave birth to twins.
[Together]
[Love... Sadness become the rain of death that falls]
Open the door, please!
[Text from Yun: Eunchae, I don't want to live anymore]
[Song Eunchae]
You have some on your face too.
Eunchae.
Let me ask you a favor.
What is it?
Instead of going to Africa, can you take care...
of Seo-yeong and Galchi?